Yaga.
What is that thing?
It is possible to have
man-made cursed corpses act
more autonomously than
other forms of manipulation.
But they're always powered by consuming
cursed energy from the sorcerer.
And yet, that thing is sustaining
itself on its own cursed energy.
The higher-ups are currently trying
to designate you as a special
grade and officially sentence
you to indefinite imprisonment.
Because if you can intentionally
create a thing like that,
then it stands to reason you
could easily create your own army.
So tell me, Yaga, you truly have
no idea how that thing was created?
Is that your official stance?
Yes.
Masamichi, everyone's worried about you.
They told me you seemed down.
Did they?
So I told them all this.
If Masamichi is feeling down,
we just have to cheer him up.
Is that so?
Pretty smart, huh?
Pretty smart.
Takeru, I'm sorry, but I have
to leave home for a while.
Would you please let
the others know for me?
Leaving for work again?
That's right.
It'll be a long trip, too.
Don't worry.
This forest is still under the
constant protection of Tengen.
And your mother will come soon.
She'll be glad to see you.
You'll be all right without me.
I'm sure of it.
Masamichi!
It sure will be lonely
around here without you.
Kusakabe, are you sure?
Just don't go telling
anyone that I helped you.
You were captured to lure Yaga out.
That's all you need to know.
Besides, I owe that man
a favor. Go on. Get.
Are you really sure about this?
This thing is not your nephew.
It's just a vessel with
your nephew's information.
Are you trying to tell
me that I can't live
in the present if I stay
hung up on the dead,
forever living in the past?
Well, my little sister can
no longer live in the past.
She needs to live in the
present, meaning with Takeru.
Masamichi, I think that
lady's my mother, isn't she?
That's right.
Good job recognizing her.
Yeah, I had a feeling that's who she was.
I must be a genius.
Sorry but don't worry I get it you can't
let anyone know that your fully autonomous
cursed corpses exist so he can't live with
her and I'm sorry why are you apologizing?
Thank you, by the way.
I mean it. Thank you.
Principal Yaga, where do you think
you're going without any cursed corpses?
I'm going to see my son.
You've been sentenced to
death, so I don't think so.
But why not save your own life?
They'll let you live if
you just tell them how you
create those fully autonomous
man-made cursed corpses.
You all sure got suddenly brave
the moment Satoru Gojo was gone.
Principal.
You may leave now.
I'll handle the rest by myself.
Understood.
First, you use the body's information
to reproduce the soul's information.
Then the soul's information is placed
inside the cursed corpse's core.
But that's not enough.
You have to place cores
that house three highly
compatible souls into
a single cursed corpse.
Then force those souls to
observe each other at all times.
Once you do that step,
it finally allows the souls to stabilize,
so self-awareness can take root.
Roughly three months after that's born,
it will begin supplying
its own cursed energy.
Why talk now?
Why are you sharing this with us now?
Why not tell us sooner?
Why not try to live longer?
Because it's...
it's a curse, Principal Gakuganji.
It's a curse that is
handed down from me to you.
Masamichi!
Why don't you fight me I assume you
hate me enough to kill me pandas
aren't bound by things like that
besides you were never on bad terms with
Masamichi to me you're just the
random knife that happened to fall
upon him but still just make sure
you remember this even pandas can cry?
Oh!
Don't know
Otona Shoko ha nahe nahe.
Love me love me.
Kuroi sa bakarete.
Love me happy.
Sampo ukaute.
Love me love me.
Aizzo mabirete.
Kako u tsulibaste. Yeah.
Aizzo Aizzo take out te.
Psycho joy yo ii tsudette.
Da ma shi da ma shi de ii no.
Da i Show nante ki mi shi nae yo.
Aizzo Aizzo ni mo Code.
Yai ko Aizzo fu ni Mode.
Bambas wando yoreshwaiyo.
Saraba Nitta haimashou.
There are probably curse users
among the participants as well,
so above all, be careful.
Why are we changing?
Hakari was expelled for
clashing with the Upper Brass.
He's also actively violating
Jujutsu regulations.
If he finds out with
Jujutsu High, he might run.
It's like we're cops and he's the robber.
Huh?
We're on Jujutsu High's side now?
We're in a gray zone.
But in Hikari's eyes at least, yeah.
Is he even likely to cooperate with us?
I'm not sure.
While our teachers say
he's a good-for-nothing.
But Okotsu claimed Takeru has the
potential to be stronger than him.
We'll definitely want his strength.
You brats better get on home.
This is no place for you
guys to be hanging out.
You have until the count
of three to turn around.
After that, I start swinging my fists.
We need money.
Let's join your little fight
club so we can earn some.
The first rule of our Fight Club is that
you do not talk about our Fight Club.
Who blabbed, and where can I find him?
If I like what you say,
I won't beat you up.
I never learned his
name, and I killed him.
It was about a month ago.
Just some scumbag who was all talk.
Kento disappeared about a month ago.
I can take his slot.
Or if you prefer, I can just beat
you to a pulp in front of your boss.
Oh, yeah.
He'd be wary if we
suddenly asked to see him.
I guess we shouldn't know
his name's Hakari, either.
No, there's no proof.
Time to zip the lips.
Are you sure?
That's enough.
The boss has given you the go-ahead.
You're lucky one of our
fighters just dropped out.
One thing, though.
Your friend's the one who's fighting.
That's good for us.
I think Dori's better suited
for this kind of thing.
No chance. I fight.
The boss said he doesn't like you.
And if you don't like
it, then the deal's off.
If that's the case, he'll fight.
Fushiguro, that was risky.
Your bluffs go too far sometimes.
You worry too much.
If curse users are participating
in the fight club too,
that means there must be decent turnover.
The curse users are here all right.
If he was watching us
through security cameras,
then there's a high chance
Akari is in there as well.
You snoop around from the inside, Itadori.
In the meantime, I'm going to
check out that parking lot.
Maybe. Maybe?
He's ignoring me for now.
If Ikari learns we're trying
to infiltrate his club,
we'll lose his trust in our
opportunity to make contact with him.
Well, we'll just resort
to force if that happens.
That really should be our last resort.
We're here for one thing.
To ask Ikari for his
cooperation in joining us.
I'd like to avoid harming
any future alliances.
To be honest, I don't think I
should be doing anything tonight.
But I don't want to waste
the time we do have until
Tsumiki is forced to
participate in the Cullen game.
Right now, it's 5 p .m. on the 10th.
So nine days until the deadline.
I guess it took us longer to get here
than we originally thought it would.
That's why I'll be looking
for Hakari tonight.
But if it looks too risky, I'll pull out.
That's why I said maybe.
Got it!
there are only two rules
no running away and no
using curse techniques
how come i don't mind if
they're using curse
techniques they won't help
them because most of the
crowd are non-sorcerers
and can't see them a
fight no one can see sucks
and the no running rule
it means you fight where
the spectators can see
you it's all about the
spectators huh they paid
to get in business 101
so what's the boss like
curious huh well yeah
you'll know if you meet
him if or when there are
two kinds of matches real
beatdowns like today's
tournament and fixed
bounce the boss writes
the script for those he
might call for you if you
manage to shine out there
you're saying to meet
the boss i just need to
put on a good show you
really can't make things
much simpler than that
Over there That's your opponent for today
I was blown away the
first time I saw him too
Yeah
It really is all about
drawing in the crowd
Are you ready to get it started?
Because it's time for the
Kachinko Fight Club Tournament
Hello everybody, I'm your commentator
for the night, John Bobby.
Allow me to introduce
tonight's exciting matchup.
We're joined by a sudden obstacle.
Will he rise up or burn out?
It's the dangerous
fireball kid, Yuji Itadori!
Please welcome Panda!
Now, take your bets!
Slice your bets!
Everyone ready to rumble!
I can feel my passion draining away.
What's wrong, my sweet baby?
If one is lucky, then
he's meant to be tested.
It's boring to gamble when you
know who will win from the start.
There aren't many stray sorcerers
who are tough enough to beat Panda.
Looks like you might be wrong.
Huh?
Panda, have you seen Hakari yet?
No.
He's not suspicious of me because we
know each other, but he's avoiding me.
Meanwhile, the other third year's
technique is also going to be a problem.
I hope you're hiding the fact
that you're from Jujutsu High.
Of course.
You know what to do now, right?
Whoa!
This is definitely the best bout
in my career as a commentator!
Even if I have only been
one for the last two weeks!
Who?
The winner, Itadori!
Hey!
That punch was a foul!
Wait, I know!
I'm gonna call the SPCA on you!
Your acting sucks. Send E.
Todori up to the roof after
he wins the tournament.
Huh?
He's sure to win it. Plus,
he's intentionally fighting
in three dimensions
to wow the spectators
in the upper rafters.
I can write a good script with him.
And like I always say...
You have to strike while the iron is hot.
I've asked you to use a
coaster a hundred times.
Got it.
And what about his buddy, the
other brat who didn't fight?
Continue to keep a close eye on him.
I'll send Kirara later as backup. Huh?
I'm feeling a buzz right now that
I haven't felt in a long time.
I haven't felt this alive since
my ex maxed out my credit cards.
I've asked you a million
times not to mention your ex.
Things are looking good.
It won't be too long before
Itadori and Hakari meet.
Tell me, Panda, why haven't you
been able to see Hakari yet?
Hmm.
Well, I do know where he likes to stay.
In the monitor room on the roof.
But I haven't been able
to get close enough.
Wait, why not?
Even when I approach the door, I
can't seem to close the distance.
The sensation feels similar
to Satoru's technique.
It's probably due to Kirara's technique.
Kirara?
But I thought the other
third-year student is a guy.
Yeah, so what?
So this, does that phenomenon only occur
when Kira-ra's in the monitor room?
I'm not sure.
I've been focusing too much
on being a circus panda
instead of pushing more
and making them run off.
I'm just really glad the
two of you showed up.
Do you think Itadori has
a chance to persuade him?
It'll be tough, but it's just a
matter of time before he does.
I think Itadori's light,
charming personality is a good
match for someone like Hakari.
But you won't believe
how bad his acting sucks.
He doesn't just suck at it.
He struggles to even
see lying as an option.
Well, that explains it, but it didn't stop
him from talking trash about my acting.
Anyway,
once Itadori enters the monitor room,
I'll buy him time by taking
control of the place.
Are you sure?
Don't worry about it.
Everything will be fine.
I know where all the cameras
and their blind spots are.
How many guards are in there?
Four at the entrance, and two on
each floor except for up on the roof.
Okay, we can handle that.
The only real concern
is Kirana's technique.
We can't do anything about that now.
If they can warp Itadori out
of there, or warp in backup,
we'll give up on pursuing Hakari.
Wow, you look so young.
Are you still a first-year Yui?
Yui?
Ken had to repeat a year in middle school.
Looks like you have a happy life here.
Well, yeah.
It's been a while since Ken's gotten
all heated up like this, though.
You see, I simply love it
when Kin is passionate.
Mitsudori,
would you believe me if I said
you can earn a million yen a
month by doing something that
takes only an hour a day to do?
Well, I guess it depends
on what that something is.
But you'll have to pay me 200,000 yen to
buy the information on what
that something is. Huh?
In that case, I don't believe you.
Good, because just like you suspected,
I was presenting you with a classic con.
The swindler pretends to be rich,
selling the means to be rich to those
desperate to be rich in a classic scam.
It's obvious if you
think about it logically,
but there's a huge number
of fools who fall for it.
And you know why?
Because it all has to do with passion.
Passion?
Both swindler and swindled
have the same passion.
They both have a compulsive drive to
change their lives for the better.
People high on passion lose
sight of their judgment.
Yet without passion, no one in
the world would ever fall in love.
I love that obsessive passion.
Do you know the most direct
way people deal with passion?
Gambling?
First time I saw you, I
knew you would get it.
After all, life is a gamble.
I can't tell you the number of women that
have dumped me because they hate gambling,
but I think they're the ones
who've got it all wrong.
Our society throws out
those who can't bet big,
as well as those who don't know when to
fold their hands and call it a night.
There isn't a single person
alive who doesn't gamble.
What people hate isn't the gambling, it's
the losing and the being ruined forever.
There must be some people who
just want to live a peaceful life.
Not anyone that I've ever met.
All the people that I know
love passion above all.
Passion equals gambling,
and gambling equals life.
And love equals control.
And I want to control this nation's
passion through my fight club one day.
With the existence of curses going public
and headquarters barely able to function,
this is my chance to expand the business.
I'm going to crush the opposition.
And I'll make them publicly
recognize my fight club
in the coming revisions to
the Jujutsu regulations.
And to do that, I'll need
a strong player on my team.
Itadori, how do you feel about
getting high on my passion?
Look, boss, I need to tell you...
I'm sorry, I haven't offered you a drink.
Oh, I'm good with anything,
really, other than liquor.
What?
Can't handle it or something?
No, it's just I'm still underage.
You don't strike me as the
type to care about that.
Did you know Gojo can't
hold his liquor either?
Yeah, who's Gojo?
And I never said that I
can't, just that I haven't.
So why the act? Huh?
There isn't a single sorcerer
who hasn't heard of Satoru Gojo.
So why did you feign ignorance? Or you?
Sent by Jujutsu High.
L-listen!
Hey! Hey!
When I get a call from Kirara's phone,
it's a signal something's fishy.
Listen!
Save it, kid!
My passion has gone cold!
it's not
I'm afraid I'm afraid I'm not
in the
I'm sure I'm looking forward
to looking forward to
that
circle